FROM ME TO YOU 2ND SEASON
FROM NOW ON
Whoa, is it really that late already?
Man... I guess time flew by while we
were working. None of us even noticed.
Are you doing okay, Sawako?
Don't forget that you're the one doing
the solo performance in the costume march
too. So just make
sure you get some sleep.
I don't mind.
Even if I weren't doing this, I
wouldn't be able to sleep tonight.
Got any extra marking pins?
Uh... Yeah!
- Sawako, your cell phone's blinking.
- Oh, you're right. Maybe it's my dad...
It's gonna be a long, long night.
Wait, you like him?!
You've got a crush on Andy, Yui?!
You should just go for it!
Yeah, Andy is a nice guy!
- Ahh! I'm so embarrassed!
- Ask him out!
I eavesdropped!
I'm making Yusuke see if he can find
out if Andy has feelings for you, too!
Sadako, do you think
they'd be a good match?
Please... Be honest, kay?
My honest thoughts...
You... You'd be... great!
Yeah... The perfect couple!
Wouldn't they be?!
Cheering and Excited Chatter)
See? You two are compatible!
- Wait... I, um...
- Sadako of the black magic café approves!
- Oh no... That was irresponsible!
- I knew it! I had a feeling it'd work out!
I think...
I am gonna try... to say something.
I bet that she's
transferring some of her power to you!
- That's so nice of her!
- That's not it...
She's extremely empathetic.
Oh man... So it's tomorrow, huh?
- We've sure come a long way.
- I bet Kazehaya's probably dying to get
in touch with her and totally frustrated.
Why are we stuck here
making this stupid float today?!
Because tomorrow's the
costume march, remember?
And we haven't made as much
progress as we should have.
Well, if Joe hadn't messed up
on the all the wood measurements...
- Oh yeah, sorry 'bout that!
- Over... and over...
I replay that same scene in my head.
Just to be sure...
That all of this...
isn't some kind of dream.
FROM: SHOTA KAZEHAYA
LET'S TALK ONCE MORE
FROM: SAWAKO KURONUMA
OKAY
Day two of the school festival.
- Oh, Chizu, you're finished?
- Yup, just lookin' for my snake.
Hey, where's Sadako?
Uh... Yano-chin's still getting her ready.
Now, open your eyes really
wide. Good. You're all finished!
Hey! How's it goin'?
Take a look.
- I mean, have you seen all the girls?
- Yeah, their costumes are hilarious!
- Aw, yours is really cute!
- Thanks!
Is... something wrong?
Uh, sorry! Just had to
check that you had legs.
I really wanted to use blush or glitter,
but I decided to go with making a strong
- first impression instead.
- I hear that you're the Okiku
- of The Dish Mansion at Banchō.
- Takahashi!
She's related to wells too, isn't she?
Just like your namesake is. By that I mean
"Sadako"
An ugly love-hate drama about a man
who couldn't be trusted and a woman who
eventually becomes enraged
by his untrustworthiness.
Is that how the story goes?
Some seem to think so.
It's a pretty juicy role.
Oh! By the way, that
mustache looks amazing on you!
I'm glad that the float and all
the costumes got finished in time.
Hold on... Why are you the
one who looks tired, Ryu?
- Because I'm going through a growth spurt.
- So, they're doing the Seven Dwarfs,
- huh? Class C's got some good taste!
- Hey.
Is this how you wear it?
I dunno. You gotta improvise.
Yano!
- Tell me, how's my talisman getup?!
- Oh uh... it's perfect! Perfectly stupid...
Awww, ya mean iiit?!
- Uhhhh you're a martial artist, right?
- Nuh-uh! I'm a snake type!
- You look good in that.
- The front's all weird.
- Oh, you think so?
- Yano.
- Where's Kuronuma?
- She was chatting in the
- hallway with Chigusa last I saw.
- Thanks.
Kazehaya.
Y'know that costume you're
wearing? It was sewn by her.
Come on! It's time to get your butts in
gear! -If you're ready to get going, then
head outside and start
lining up! -That's odd.
Huh? What?
Where'd Kuronuma go?
If you're looking for her
she's already out there.
Ah okay, thanks. Why
is he in such a hurry?
Off to get rejected again?
If you think I care, I don't. Sorry!
Wait... He looked so vibrant
and full of life just now!
How is that possible when he was so
down in the dumps not that long ago!
- What's it to you?
- Can you move?
Listen, just do your best for your solo.
I bet you anything Shota
would say the same thing.
Kuronuma!
This is why... I wanna
hide you from everyone.
Thanks a lot for the message.
I, uh no, thank you.
Kazehaya! Do you think all the girls in
school will dig me if I hop around while
- I'm wearing this?
- Hey, just give me a second.
This is tiring...
Yeah sorry. I'm talking to Kuronuma.
NAMU AMIDA BUTSU
Huh? What's up guys...?
Kuronuma, I wanna tell you again.
And I wanna say it right.
Um...
But do you mind if I say
what I have to say first?
Please... before my courage runs out...
I was... happy to be with you at
the shrine, on New Years Eve.
To be honest... really
happy and it scared me.
There was one side of me that wanted to
make you all mine but the other side
didn't want to risk
being disliked by you.
If I share my feelings with
him, it could change everything.
Then again...
I really... would like to form a new
relationship with you, Kazehaya.
From now on, We'll both be starting over!
I think... whatever comes out of this...
Because it's with
Kazehaya, then I'm sure... I'm sure...
Gather round!
Please watch me.
I'll do my best.
There are so many things in my life that
have changed after having met you. Using
all of my experiences from the past
year, I'm going to give the most vengeful
performance ever!
I'll do what I can to
help our class win this!
When I realized I liked
Kazehaya... I noticed a change in myself.
Kuronuma!
I like you!
NIGHT PARADE OF DEMONS
Hey, tell me.
Just now... What
exactly do you mean by that?
A-A compliment!
I want...
...to be... closer with everyone.
I'll try my best to become
friends... with both of them!
AROMA HABO TEA
I mean it. I don't
need you to be my savior.
Alright?
TETSURYUKEN
Next up... will be Class 2-D.
Number one...
And number two...
Ah... my prized plates...
No matter how many times I
count, there's always one missing...
Now's the time! Do it!
TSUBUKO
I've kept them cooled, so they're as
cold as ice. I hope you enjoy them...
- Do you think these are bribes?
- What else could they be?
Can you... stop staring? It's scary.
Ah, hello everyone. After such an eventful
day, it's time to begin the 43rd Kitahoro
High School Festival's closing ceremony.
To start off, we will
announce each divisions' rankings.
1st place in the hallway flier division...
...is Class 3-B with their Wild West theme!
And 1st place in the food
stand division goes to... Class 2-D!
The black magic consultation's high
popularity put them at a solid 1st place!
Sa-da-ko! Sa-da-ko! Sa-da-ko! Sa-da-ko!
- Sa-da-ko! Sa-da-ko! Sa-da-ko! Sa-da-ko!
- Next up... the results
of the costume march.
We've got this in the bag!
Now, unfortunately for Class 2-D, the
drinks served to the judges during their
performance have been determined to be
bribery. Therefore, Class 2-D earned zero
points for the costume march.
- What?
- Thanks for understanding.
Now, the moment we've all been
waiting for, it's time to announce the
- total ranking!
- Are you kidding me?!
Screw all that! Now you listen to me...
Ulterior motives... come straight from the
heart!
The class that came out on top
for this year's Grand Prize is...
Fatty tuna! Sea urchin!
Abaloneee!
So, we ended up in 6th place at the end.
But we were 1st place
among the 2nd-year classes.
We were actually pretty close.
If there weren't bribes, we
could've placed on the costume march too.
Yeah, since Sadako's
acting was so spot on!
- The after-party'll be at the usual place.
- Good to know. Sawako.
They're not different.
They're the same, aren't they?
I kept thinking, "It can't be."
But deep down, there was little one
possibility I could never cross out.
I like you!
I want all of it...
I... I want everything, Kazehaya.
Me too.
It's like a dream.
They finally reached you.
I like you more than anyone.
His blushing face...
The faint sea breeze...
Next time: "After the Festival"